Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS.357
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Video recordings, 1976 - 1988; 243787
  - Nelson's Family in South Carolina, Feburary 1986; ID: 357.0230; 244691 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0230, Case 357.0230)
    February 24, 25, 26, 1986 Featuring: Nancy, Mama, Doris, Fred, Emma, Henry, Doris + Harry, Mrs. Mobley, Nancy - [Manot Care], Billie Jo, Peek Sisters Music Video
  - Keith Haring "Into 1984" New Year's Party, December 31, 1984; ID: 357.0231; 244694 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0231)
  - Mama Said, undated; ID: 357.0232; 244695 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0232, Case 357.0232)
  - Wigstock #1, August 18, 1985; ID: 357.0233; 244696 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0233, Case 357.0233_pt.1, Case 357.0233_pt.2)
  - Wigstock #2 (part 3), September 1, 1986; ID: 357.0240; 251115 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0240, Case 357.0240)
    Original format: Video8mm
  - Bobby and Mary Kaye's Wedding, October 11, 1986; ID: 357.0234; 244700 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0234, Case 357.0234)
  - Stringfellow's Fashion Show #1, Now Explosion at Pyramid, May 25, 1988; ID: 357.0235; 244701 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0235, Case 357.0235/357.0236)
    Featuring: Mandingo and RuPaul singing Bad Bad Bad
  - Neurotic Theatrical Co., November 30, 1986; ID: 357.0236; 244702 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0236, Case 357.0235/357.0236)
  - Snow Angel with Sylvia Miles, 1985; ID: 357.0237; 244703 (Box 8, Media ID: 357.0237, Case 357.0237)
  - Now Explosion at Limelight, Bunny at Pyramid, November 24, 1986; ID: 357.0238; 251112 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0238, Case 357.0238)
  - Fred's Anti Theatre at Limelight with great pies, July 13, 1986; ID: 357.0239; 251114 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0239)
  - Now Explosion Central Park and Van, May 18, 1986; ID: 357.0241; 251116 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0241)
  - Now Explosion TIF, Man 2 Man at The Saint, WHISPERS at Pyramid with Lady Bunny, New Music Seminar with RuPaul, July 1986; ID: 357.0242; 251117 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0242, Case 357.0242)
    [1] -- Now Explosion TIF, 7/14/1986 [2] -- Man 2 Man at The Saint, 7/15/1986 [3] -- WHISPERS at Pyramid with Lady Bunny, 7/15/1986 [4] -- New Music Seminar with RuPaul, 7/15/1988
  - Vicki's Party, July 27, 1987; ID: 357.0243; 251118 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0243, Case 357.0243)
  - Phyllis Tarter at Williams Residence, October 20, 1988; ID: 357.0244; 251119 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0244, Case 357.0244)
  - A Coupla White Chicks (raw footage), April 12, 1987; ID: 357.0245; 251120 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0245, Case 357.0245)
  - People Tree at Pyramid, October 7, 1987; ID: 357.0246; 251122 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0246, Case 357.0246)
  - Celebrity Club with Bunny, August 30, 1988; ID: 357.0247; 251123 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0247, Case 357.0247)
  - People Tree at Pyramid, May 29, 1988; ID: 357.0248; 251124 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0248, Case 357.0248)
  - Pyramid Celebrates new management, Pattelson's, G. Gnt., 5th Avenue, East Village, Eddie, Perry, etc., June 4, 1986; ID: 357.0249; 251125 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0249, Case 357.0249)
    [1] -- Pyramid Celebrates new management, 6/4/1986 [2] -- Pattelson's, G. Gnt., 5th Avenue, East Village, Eddie, Perry, etc., 10/5/1986
  - Celebrity Club, August 24, 1988; ID: 357.0250; 251126 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0250, Case 357.0250)
  - Pop Tarts D&D, Now Explosion show for New Music Seminar at Limelight, July 16, 1986; ID: 357.0251; 251127 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0251)
  - Now Explosion Times Square to East Village (Now Explosion outside Pyramid Club), undated; ID: 357.0252; 251129 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0252, Case 357.0252)
  - Anti Theatre Wedding, July 19, 1986; ID: 357.0253; 251133 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0253, Case 357.0253)
  - Phyllis Tarter Phantom of the Opera, February 1, 1987; ID: 357.0254; 251136 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0254, Case 357.0254)
  - Celebrity Club, September 14, 1988; ID: 357.0255; 251138 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0255)
  - Flaunt It #2, December 7, 1986; ID: 357.0256; 251139 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0256, Case 357.0256)
  - Pyramid Birthday #5, Flaunt It #3, December 14, 1986; ID: 357.0257; 251140 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0257, Case 357.0257)
  - Pyramid 5th Birthday (tape #2), ED, December 1987; ID: 357.0258; 251142 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0258, Case 357.0258)
    [1] -- Pyramid 5th Birthday (tape #2), 12/14/1986 [2] -- ED, 12/17/1986
  - Pop Tarts at The Saint, November 13, 1986; ID: 357.0259; 251143 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0259, Case 357.0259)
  - Dial M for Model (#2) at Limelight, November 11, 1986; ID: 357.0260; 251147 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0260, Case 357.0260)
  - Kennon, Dial M for Model, Clayton's Pryamid Photo session, November 1986; ID: 357.0261; 251149 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0261, Case 357.0261)
    [1] -- Kennon, 11/10/1986 [2] -- Dial M for Model, 11/10/1986 [3] -- Clayton's Pryamid Photo session, 11/11/1986
  - L. Mandenbaum's Birthday at Madame Rosa's, Drag Ball (part 2), 1986; ID: 357.0262; 251155 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0262, Case 357.0262)
    [1] -- L. Mandenbaum's Birthday at Madame Rosa's, 9/6/1986 [2] -- Drag Ball (part 2), 10/24/1986
  - Andrea Fault at Pyramid, November 15, 1986; ID: 357.0263; 251158 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0263, Case 357.0263)
  - The Last Moments of 1986, December 31, 1986; ID: 357.0264; 251160 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0264)
  - Phyllis Tarter Recital, June 14, 1986; ID: 357.0265; 251164 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0265, Case 357.0265)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid with Hapi Phace, Tabboo!, ML, Ethel Eichelberger, Tompkins Square Park (Kennon, Conch, Folk singer), June 1986; ID: 357.0266; 251168 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0266, Case 357.0266)
    [1] -- WHISPERS at Pyramid with Hapi Phace, Tabboo!, ML, Ethel Eichelberger, 6/14/1986 [2] -- Tompkins Square Park (Kennon, Conch, Folk singer), 6/15/1986
  - Drag Queen Olympics at Pyramid, July 9, 1986; ID: 357.0267; 251172 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0267)
  - Tabboo! At Pyramid, Kill Pig, Quando, September 27, 1986; ID: 357.0268; 251174 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0268, Case 357.0268)
  - Dean Johnson's Birthday Barbecue and Show at The World, May 31, 1988; ID: 357.0269; 251179 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0269, Case 357.0269)
  - Lypsinka, La Palace de Beaute, John Sex, September 25, 1988; ID: 357.0270; 251180 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0270, Case 357.0270_pt.1, Case 357.0270_pt.2)
    DVD access available. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
  - Celebrity Club with Hapi Phace, Lizette, Lurleen, September 7, 1988; ID: 357.0271; 251181 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0271, Case 357.0271)
  - John Sex at Red Garter, Marlene at Pyramid, Disco Van, September 10, 1988; ID: 357.0272; 251185 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0272, Case 357.0272_pt.1, Case 357.0272_pt.2)
  - Mrs. Sullivan and Aunt Doris in NYC, May 1986; ID: 357.0273; 251188 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0273, Case 357.0273)
    [1] -- Mrs. Sullivan and Aunt Doris in NYC, 5/26/1986 [2] -- Mrs. Sullivan and Aunt Doris in NYC, 5/27/1986
  - Limelight - Coney Island, May 27, 1986; ID: 357.0274; 251189 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0274, Case 357.0274)
  - Edit for Tunnel, January 14, 1988; ID: 357.0275; 251190 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0275, Case 357.0275)
  - Wigstock III (#4), Rockets & Dave, Kennon (part 1), September 1987; ID: 357.0276; 251191 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0276, Case 357.0276_pt.1, Case 357.0276_pt.2)
    [1] -- Wigstock III (#4), Rockets & Dave, 9/7/1987 [2] -- Kennon (part 1), 9/10/1987
  - RuPaul fr. Erll to Grand Central, DV8 Trip to Boston (part 1), April 1988; ID: 357.0277; 251194 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0277, Case 357.0277)
    [1] -- RuPaul fr. Erll to Grand Central, 4/21/1988 [2] -- DV8 Trip to Boston (part 1), 4/22/1988
  - Bobby Surprise Party, Celebrity Club, September 1988; ID: 357.0278; 251197 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0278, Case 357.0278)
    [1] -- Bobby surprise party, 7/18/1988 [2] -- Celebrity Club, 7/21/1988
  - Nasomi/Kill Pig - Limelight, East Village, Eddie, September 23, 1986; ID: 357.0280; 251203 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0280, Case 357.0280)
  - Randy Pop's Birthday at Cafe de la Place, September 22, 1986; ID: 357.0281; 251207 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0281, Case 357.0281)
  - RuPaul Limelight - Spicey, Trade, Albert, Michael Musto, Dick (part 2), September 2, 1986; ID: 357.0282; 251208 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0282, Case 357.0282)
  - RuPaul Limelight (part 1), RuPaul / Sushi / Avenue A, September 20, 1986; ID: 357.0283; 251209 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0283, Case 357.0283)
  - The Wizard of Oz at Pyramid, Dainty (abortion), September 17, 1986; ID: 357.0284; 251211 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0284, Case 357.0284_pt.1, Case 357.0284_pt.2)
  - Candy Store/Quando, November 14, 1986; ID: 357.0285; 251213 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0285, Case 357.0285)
  - Bobby and Mary Kaye's Wedding, October 11, 1986; ID: 357.0286; 251241 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0286, Case 357.0286)
  - Floyd's fashions at Tunnel, Lisa E "Positive Me" (take #1), 1988; ID: 357.0287; 251243 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0287, Case 357.0287)
    [1] -- Floyd's fashions at Tunnel, 10/13/1988 [2] -- Lisa E "Positive Me" (take #1), 10/15/1988
  - Richard Metzger's film crew at 5 Ninth Avenue, October 1, 1988; ID: 357.0288; 251245 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0288, Case 357.0288)
  - Wigstock IV (part 3), August 31, 1988; ID: 357.0289; 251246 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0289, Case 357.0289)
  - Wigstock III (part 2), September 7, 1987; ID: 357.0279; 251200 (Box 9, Media ID: 357.0279, Case 357.0279)
  - Limelight Drag Show, October 12, 1986; ID: 357.0290; 251248 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0290, Case 357.0290)
  - World Welcomes Michael Alig, Me and BBC, Me with Pop Tarts editing BBC piece, 1989; ID: 357.0291; 251249 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0291, Case 357.0291_pt.1, Case 357.0291_pt.2)
    [1] -- World Welcomes Michael Alig, 1/12/1989 [2] -- Me and BBC, 1/15/1989 [3] -- Me with Pop Tarts editing BBC piece, 1/22/1989
  - Karen's Birthday, June 20, 1986; ID: 357.0292; 251250 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0292, Case 357.0292)
  - Liz at Palladium, Michael Musto, May 1986; ID: 357.0293; 251251 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0293, Case 357.0293)
    [1] -- Liz at Palladium, 5/24/1986 [2] -- Michael Musto, 5/25/1986
  - MIX TAPE Craig Vandenberg edit, undated; ID: 357.0294; 251252 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0294, Case 357.0294)
  - Calendar Boy Contest at Rock and Roll Fag Bar, November 29, 1988; ID: 357.0295; 251253 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0295, Case 357.0295)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid with Jayne County and Wendy Wild (with Trade and Jance), October 2, 1988; ID: 357.0296; 251254 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0296, Case 357.0296)
  - Bn on TV, Dick, Palladium, Beach Party, James St. James in Deli, Limelight, Albert & Liz walk to studio with for RuPaul's Starbooty recording session, May 1986; ID: 357.0297; 251255 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0297, Case 357.0297)
    [1] -- Bn on TV, Dick, Palladium, Beach Party, James St. James in Deli, Limelight, 5/24/1986 [2] -- Albert & Liz walk to studio with for RuPaul's Starbooty recording session, 5/25/1986
  - International Chrysis at Boy Bar, Sister Dimension at Wah Wah Hut, November 17, 1988; ID: 357.0298; 251256 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0298)
  - Mars - First Sunday with Trade, undated; ID: 357.0299; 251257 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0299, Case 357.0299/357.0300)
  - Test Tape, undated; ID: 357.0300; 251259 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0300, Case 357.0299/357.0300)
  - Blackout in snow, People Tree at Pyramid, 1988; ID: 357.0301; 251260 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0301, Case 357.0301)
    [1] -- Blackout in snow, 1/3/1988 [2] -- People Tree at Pyramid, 1/3/1988
  - Pyramid Club Birthday # 7, December 10, 1988; ID: 357.0302; 251261 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0302, Case 357.0302)
  - Phyllis Tartar & Co. St. Saeric (part 1), June 4, 1989; ID: 357.0303; 251262 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0303, Case 357.0303)
  - Phyllis Tartar & Co. St. Saeric (part 2), June 4, 1989; ID: 357.0304; 251278 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0304, Case 357.0304)
  - DV8 trip to Washington on bus, Judy Garlands on Parade on Christopher Street, June 1989; ID: 357.0305; 251280 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0305, Case 357.0305_pt.1, Case 357.0305_pt.2)
    [1] -- DV8 trip to Washington on bus, 6/21/1989 [2] -- Judy Garlands on Parade on Christopher Street, 6/23/1989
  - Trip to Atlanta airport, Atlanta, Nancy, February 1 and 2, 1989; ID: 357.0306; 251282 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0306, Case 357.0306)
  - Big Star on Ponce de Leon February, Lennox Square, Molly's, The American Music Show, February 1989; ID: 357.0307; 251285 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0307, Case 357.0307)
    [1] -- Big Star on Ponce de Leon February, 2/8/1989 [2] -- Lennox Square, Molly's, The American Music Show, 2/9/1989
  - San Francisco Mix #1, undated; ID: 357.0308; 251286 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0308, Case 357.0308)
  - Love Ball, Susanne Bartsch at Roseland, May 10, 1989; ID: 357.0309; 251288 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0309, Case 357.0309)
  - Morning at 5 Ninth Avenue, July 4th (part 2), International Chrysis with Man 2 Man at Limelight, Philly's Birthday, July 4, 1986; ID: 357.0310; 251291 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0310, Case 357.0310)
    [1] -- Morning at 5 Ninth Avenue, 7/4/1986 [2] -- July 4th 1986 (part 2), 7/4/1986 [3] -- International Chrysis with Man 2 Man at Limelight, 7/6/1986 [4] -- Philly's Birthday, 7/9/1986
  - Flaunt It Club #1 with Phoebe Legere at Limelight, November 30, 1986; ID: 357.0311; 251293 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0311, Case 357.0311)
  - Dave Smith, Jasmine, Dawn Houston, Eddie, December 3, 1986; ID: 357.0312; 251294 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0312, Case 357.0312)
  - The Nelson and Eddie Christmas Special, December 25, 1986; ID: 357.0313; 251296 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0313, Case 357.0313)
  - Eddie, Phoebe Legere at Freddie's, October 15, 1986; ID: 357.0314; 251297 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0314, Case 357.0314)
  - Flaunt It #4, December 21, 1986; ID: 357.0315; 251299 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0315, Case 357.0315)
  - Leigh Bowery,Tom Rubnitz & Charles Atlas Birthday at John Badam's Apartment, Albert Crudo Fashion Show at Red Zone, April 3, 1989; ID: 357.0316; 251300 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0316, Case 357.0316_pt.1, Case 357.0316_pt.2)
  - San Francisco Tapes, February 6, 1987; ID: 357.0317; 251302 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0317, Case 357.0317)
  - Atlanta #2, 1987; ID: 357.0318; 251341 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0318, Case 357.0318)
  - Albert Crudo, Eric Conrad and Frank Owen, Passion Rip at Tunnel (Fashion Show), March 1987; ID: 357.0319; 251342 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0319, Case 357.0319)
    [1] -- Albert Crudo, Eric Conrad and Frank Owen, 3/4/1987 [2] -- Passion Rip at Tunnel (Fashion Show), 3/12/1987
  - Copy of Pyramid, Kennon at Pyramid, 1986-1987; ID: 357.0320; 251344 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0320, Case 357.0320)
    [1] -- Copy of Pyramid, 9/26/1986 [2] -- Kennon at Pyramid, 2/24/1987
  - Celebrity Club at The World, March 9, 1989; ID: 357.0321; 251345 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0321, Case 357.0321)
  - S. Freedman at The World, Michael Alig Christmas, Bunny Christmas, December 1988; ID: 357.0322; 251346 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0322, Case 357.0322)
    [1] -- S. Freedman at The World, 12/23/1988 [2] -- Michael Alig Christmas, 12/24/1988 [3] -- Bunny Christmas, 12/24/1988
  - Apple Love at Mars, May 28, 1989; ID: 357.0323; 251348 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0323, Case 357.0323)
  - La Palace de Beaute (part 1), October 10, 1987; ID: 357.0324; 251349 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0324, Case 357.0324)
  - Freddy & Michael Musto at The World, Bunny at Boy Bar, 1987-1988; ID: 357.0325; 251350 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0325, Case 357.0325)
  - Kenny at The World - Fag Bar, Michelangelo Signorelli and Michael Musto, Christina at The Tunnel, December 1987; ID: 357.0326; 251352 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0326, Case 357.0326)
    [1] -- Kenny at The World - Fag Bar, 12/1/1987 [2] -- Michelangelo Signorelli and Michael Musto, 12/9/1987 [3] -- Christina at The Tunnel, 12/25/1987
  - Atlanta, Monday, Pop Tarts, Michael Musto and Albert Leave, 2200 Beaver Creek, 2900 Kershaw, 3600 Nancy, July 4, 1988; ID: 357.0327; 251354 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0327, Case 357.0327)
  - Provincetown, Boston, Michael Musto, Alice #6, August 14 and 15, 1986; ID: 357.0328; 251355 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0328, Case 357.0328)
  - Rock & Roll Fag Bar at The World, House Tour, 1987; ID: 357.0329; 251358 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0329, Case 357.0329)
    [1] -- Rock & Roll Fag Bar at The World, 9/22/1987 [2] -- House Tour, 10/24/1987
  - Nelson's Hernia Operation, June 9, 1987; ID: 357.0330; 251361 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0330, Case 357.0330)
  - Bad Tape, undated; ID: 357.0331; 251363 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0331)
  - Christina, East Village, Carlo's party, April 14, 1989; ID: 357.0332; 251364 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0332, Case 357.0332)
  - A.A. Mix, undated; ID: 357.0333; 251365 (Box 10, Media ID: 357.0333, Case 357.0333)
  - Atlanta #10, Sophie's Cabin, August 22, 1987; ID: 357.0334; 251373 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0334, Case 357.0334)
  - Vito's Boat Party #1, undated; ID: 357.0335; 251375 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0335, Case 357.0335)
  - La Palace with RuPaul at Pyramid, January 30, 1988; ID: 357.0336; 251380 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0336, Case 357.0336)
  - La Palace at Tunnel, January 22, 1988; ID: 357.0337; 251382 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0337, Case 357.0337)
  - Fred as Rocco at The World, May 5, 1988; ID: 357.0338; 251385 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0338)
  - John, Rhonda, Blackout and Me at Pier, Deee-Lite at The World, Sex Toys at Tunnel, 1988; ID: 357.0339; 251388 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0339, Case 357.0339)
    [1] -- John, Rhonda, Blackout and Me at Pier, 5/28/1988 [2] -- Deee-Lite at The World, 6/3/1988 [3] -- Sex Toys at Tunnel, 6/3/1988
  - John Sex Bad Boys, John Sex at 5 Ninth watching himself on Japanese TV, Vito's Birthday, June 1986; ID: 357.0340; 251389 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0340, Case 357.0340)
    [1] -- John Sex Bad Boys, 6/15/1986 [2] -- John Sex at 5 Ninth watching himself on Japanese TV, 6/17/1986 [3] -- Vito's Birthday, 6/18/1986
  - La Palace de Beaute (part 3), October 10, 1987; ID: 357.0341; 251391 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0341, Case 357.0341_pt.1, Case 357.0341_pt.2)
  - Woodstock IV (part 2), August 31, 1988; ID: 357.0343; 251393 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0343, Case 357.0343_pt.1, Case 357.0343_pt.2)
  - Albert's Fashions at Red Zone, April 1, 1989; ID: 357.0344; 251395 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0344, Case 357.0344)
  - My Christmas Party at Tunnel, Alexis del Lago at The World, 1987-1988; ID: 357.0345; 251396 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0345, Case 357.0345)
    [1] -- My Christmas Party at Tunnel, 12/23/1987 [2] -- Alexis del Lago at The World, 1/3/1988
  - Brenda and Brandy at Limelight, Apollo Mystery Concert 2 (part 1), March 31, 1988; ID: 357.0346; 251398 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0346, Case 357.0346)
    Original format: Video8mm; Preseration note: the original tape is missing from the cassette.
  - Atlanta #7 - Playboy music video, August 20, 1987; ID: 357.0347; 251400 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0347, Case 357.0347)
  - Celebrity Club with Albert, Michael Musto, Fashion Patrol, Christina, August 10, 1988; ID: 357.0348; 251402 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0348, Case 357.0348)
  - New York to San Francisco #1, February 1986; ID: 357.0349; 251403 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0349, Case 357.0349)
    [1] -- New York to San Francisco, 2/11/1986-2/13/1986
  - Bride Party, Vicki's Party, June 1988; ID: 357.0350; 251404 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0350, Case 357.0350)
    [1] -- Bride Party, 6/25/1988 [2] -- Vicki's Party, 6/26/1988
  - RuPaul Voyeur Party at Tunnel, undated; ID: 357.0351; 251405 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0351, Case 357.0351)
  - Bunny Show at Pyramid (part 2), February 3, 1988; ID: 357.0352; 251406 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0352, Case 357.0352)
  - Atlanta #5 Judy LaGrange Show, Provincetown, August 10, 1986; ID: 357.0353; 251408 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0353, Case 357.0353)
  - Tabboo! & Alexis del Lago Pyramid, July 26, 1987; ID: 357.0354; 251409 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0354, Case 357.0354_pt.1, Case 357.0354_pt.2)
    DVD access copy availale. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
  - Tunnel Benefit and After the Show, Samantha Fox Video Shoot in Front of 5 Ninth Avenue, April 4, 1988; ID: 357.0355; 251410 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0355, Case 357.0355)
  - Leather Limelight, October 4, 1987; ID: 357.0356; 251412 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0356, Case 357.0356)
  - Friday at 4-D, Albert at World Trade Center,Tunnel Sunday, Liz's Party, March 1987; ID: 357.0357; 251413 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0357, Case 357.0357)
    [1] -- Friday at 4-D, 3/27/1987 [2] -- Albert at World Trade Center, 3/29/1987 [3] -- Tunnel Sunday, 3/29/1987 [4] -- Liz's Party
  - Atlanta #4, August 1987; ID: 357.0358; 251414 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0358, Case 357.0358)
    [1] -- Atlanta #4, 8/16/1987-8/17/1987
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid, May 17, 1986; ID: 357.0359; 251415 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0359, Case 357.0359)
  - Alice Bost, Zora at Green Street, November 3, 1987; ID: 357.0360; 251416 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0360, Case 357.0360)
  - Shopping in Columbia, South Carolina, February 4, 1989; ID: 357.0361; 251417 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0361, Case 357.0361)
  - Zette at The World, RuPaul to East Village, May 1986; ID: 357.0362; 251418 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0362, Case 357.0362)
    [1] -- Zette at The World, 5/13/1986 [2] -- RuPaul to East Village, 5/22/1986
  - Susanne Bartsch at Copacabana, Weather Girls, October 29, 1988; ID: 357.0363; 251419 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0363, Case 357.0363)
  - Porn 3, undated; ID: 357.0364; 251420 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0364)
    [1] -- Porn 3, not a Nelson Sullivan tape
  - East Village Sunday, June 22, 1986; ID: 357.0365; 251421 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0365, Case 357.0365)
  - Candy Store, November 15, 1986; ID: 357.0366; 251422 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0366, Case 357.0366)
  - Liz's Party, Avenue B and 6th Street, January 11, 1987; ID: 357.0367; 251425 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0367, Case 357.0367)
  - Palladium #2 Downtown Party & Sister Dimension, May 28, 1986; ID: 357.0368; 251426 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0368, Case 357.0368)
  - Zette at Pyramid, March 21, 1987; ID: 357.0369; 251428 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0369, Case 357.0369)
  - May 17, 1987 (part 2), ID: 357.0370; 251429 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0370, Case 357.0370)
  - Gay Day Pyramid People, 1986; ID: 357.0371; 251430 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0371, Case 357.0371)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid (with Ethel Eichelberger, Tabboo!, Maize, Pet., Ger., etc.), Dean Johnson at Pyramid, 5 Ninth Avenue (with John Epperson to East Village), RuPaul at Jane West Hotel, June 8, 1986; ID: 357.0372; 251433 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0372, Case 357.0372_pt.1, Case 357.0372_pt.2)
  - Katia Gallas, December 4, 1988; ID: 357.0373; 251435 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0373, Case 357.0373)
  - Christina's Apartment, Obsessions, November 1988; ID: 357.0374; 251437 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0374, Case 357.0374_pt.1, Case 357.0374_pt.2)
    [1] -- Christina's Apartment, 11/11/1988 [2] -- Obsessions, 11/12/1988
  - Susanne Bartsch Copacabana Village People, August 25, 1988; ID: 357.0375; 251440 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0375, Case 357.0375_pt.1, Case 357.0375_pt.2)
    Existence and Location of Originals
  - Eddie, Pop Tarts, Albert, Me in a Car, September 15, 1988; ID: 357.0376; 251442 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0376, Case 357.0376)
  - Disco 88 and MTV, Michael Musto, The World, March 29, 1988; ID: 357.0377; 251444 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0377, Case 357.0377)
  - Limelight Da DA, January 20, 1988; ID: 357.0378; 251445 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0378, Case 357.0378)
  - Gay Day Night at Limelight, June 29, 1986; ID: 357.0379; 251446 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0379, Case 357.0379)
  - Dale Livingston and Phil Mealy at the Montclair Art Museum, March 20, 1988; ID: 357.0380; 251447 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0380)
  - John Sex with Wendy Wild and Chicklet at Pyramid, Changing of the Guard (part 2), March 1988; ID: 357.0381; 251449 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0381, Case 357.0381)
    [1] -- John Sex (with Wendy Wild and Chicklet) at Pyramid, 3/9/1988 [2] -- Changing of the Guard (part 2), 3/12/1988
  - My 40th Birthday at Pyramid, March 15, 1988; ID: 357.0382; 251452 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0382, Case 357.0382)
  - Downtown Dukes and Divas, November 15, 1987; ID: 357.0383; 251456 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0383, Case 357.0383)